Guide to the UE Local 610 Records, 1937-1990 UE.16.610
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Grievances, 1942-1988; 16.610.6.
  - Grievances: Section 63, 1965-1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Grievances: Section 64, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Grievances: Section 69, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Grievances: Data Center, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Grievances: Employees Applications for Transfers, 1955-1973 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Grievances: EP#1 - Pavliar, 1974-1982 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Grievances: EP#2 - Ramsey, 1973-1981 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Grievances: Salary, 1981-1986 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Grievances: Salary - Resolved, 1982-1985 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Grievances: Unsettled, 1960-1965 (Box 15, Folder 27-28)
  - Verbal Grievances: ER, 1954-1965 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Verbal Grievances: General, 1955-1965 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Verbal Grievances: Piece Rate, 1955-1960 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Verbal Grievances: Seniority, 1955-1959 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Verbal Grievances: Suspensions, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Verbal Grievances: Timestudy, 1955-1960 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Verbal Grievances: Upgrading, 1955-1960 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Absenteeism, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Alcoholic Cases, [RESTRICTED], 1976-1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - B, 1977-1980 (Box 16, Folder 03-04)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1974-1978 (Box 16, Folder 05-15)
  - Insubordination, 1978-1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Insurance: Cherkun, Charles, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Insurance: General, 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - M, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Merit Increases, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971-1978 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1973-1983 (Box 16, Folder 22-26)
  - N, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Pending, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Pension, 1971-1974 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Piecework, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - S, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Section 220, 310-320, 1971-1976 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Section 541, 544, 553, 1976-1981 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Settled, 1972-1981 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Short Order Rates, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Social Security, 1973-1978 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Terminations and Discharges, [RESTRICTED], 1972-1978 (Box 16, Folder 37-38)
  - Unemployment Compensation, 1975-1979 (Box 16, Folder 39-40)
  - Weekly Indemnity Insurance Plan, 1970-1974 (Box 16, Folder 41-42)
  - Worker's Compensation, 1972-1978 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - A, 1978-1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - B, 1981-1985 (Box 17, Folder 02-03)
  - C, 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 04-07)
  - D-E, 1980-1984 (Box 17, Folder 08-09)
  - Engineers doing Bargaining Unit Work, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - ER Update, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - F-G, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - H, 1980-1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - J, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 14-16)
  - K, 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 17-18)
  - L, 1981-1988 (Box 17, Folder 19-21)
  - M, 1978-1986 (Box 17, Folder 22-27)
  - N-P, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - National Labor Relations Board - Gearshaper, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - R, 1981-1984 (Box 17, Folder 30-31)
  - S, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Salary - Job Descriptions, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Salary - To Be Resolved, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Seniority Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Severance Pay, 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - S, 1981-1983 (Box 17, Folder 37-38)
  - T-V, 1982-1985 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Tools Lost During Strike, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Treasury Department, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Truckers, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - W-Y, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 43-44)
  - Third Step, 1982-1987 (Box 17, Folder 45-47)
- Arbitrations, 1940-1985; 16.610.7.
  Acces to Box 20 Folder 34 a signed confidentiality agreement.
  These files originate from both the Airbrake and Switch divisions and date from 1940 to 1985. Materials are arranged alphabetically by either employee name or topic. One box of arbitrations dates from 1940 to 1949 and contains several War Labor Board cases. Several files exist for arbitrations generated from departmental grievances and are therefore arranged by department. Other arbitrations refer to individual employees or specialized issues such as veterans' re-employment or vacation rights, length of the workweek, contract negotiations, wage increases, and piece rates.
  The two remaining boxes date from 1955 to 1985 and contain arbitrations concerning employees or specific issues. More extensive files exist for the Briney arbitration, in which Local 610 members Harold Briney and Theodore Wright were suspended from employment for utilizing the Fifth Amendment during an examination by the House Un-American Activities Committee. Extensive files also exist for arbitrations concerning female retirement and pensions, and unjustified or suspicious discharges and suspensions. Also included in this series is information on unemployment compensation during the 1960s.
  - Airbrake Division: Department AC, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Airbrake Division: Department CD, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Airbrake Division: Department CP - Packers Pool, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Airbrake Division: Department G, 1944, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 04-05)
  - Airbrake Division: Department O, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Airbrake Division: Department U, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Airbrake Division: Discharge, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Airbrake Division: Grievances, 1940-1947 (Box 18, Folder 09-10)
  - Airbrake Division: Time Study Grievance, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Airbrake Division: Transfer Based on Seniority, 1945 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Airbrake Division: Veteran's Re-employment, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - War Labor Board Cases: Bargaining Unit for Patrolmen/Watchmen, 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 14-15)
  - War Labor Board Cases: Miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - War Labor Board Cases: Work Week, 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Airbrake and Union Switch and Signal: Miscellaneous, 1944-1949 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Airbrake and Union Switch and Signal: Veteran's Vacation, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Airbrake and Union Switch and Signal: Contract Arbitration, 1944-1947 (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
  - Airbrake and Union Switch and Signal: Piece Rates, 1943-1945 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Airbrake and Union Switch and Signal: Wage Increases, 1943-1944 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Airbrake and Union Switch and Signal: Work Week, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Union Switch and Signal Division: Department 34, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Union Switch and Signal Division: Department 35, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Union Switch and Signal Division: Department 38, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Union Switch and Signal Division: Department 35 and 70, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Union Switch and Signal Division: Department 70, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Union Switch and Signal Division: Department 77, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - A, 1974-1985 (Box 19, Folder 01-02)
  - Awards, 1978-1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Briney, Harold: Employment, 1953-1959 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Briney, Harold: Transcript of Testimony, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Briney and Wright: Arbitration, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 09-11)
  - Briney and Wright: Correspondence with Company, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Briney and Wright: Publicity, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Briney and Wright: Related Cases, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Briney and Wright: Support, 1955 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Calibration Recall, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - C, 1970-1979 (Box 19, Folder 17-18)
  - CP Hot Press, 1948-1949 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Discharge Grievance and Collective Agreement: General, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Discharge Grievance and Collective Agreement: Legal Briefs, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - D, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - F, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Female Pensions, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Female Retirement: Company Exhibits, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Female Retirement: Official Transcript, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Female Retirement: Post-Hearing Brief, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Female Retirement: Reply on Behalf of the Union, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Female Retirement: Statement on Behalf of the Union, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Female Retirement: Supporting Materials, 1959-1962 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - G, 1973-1983 (Box 20, Folder 01-04)
  - Hardy, Richard, 1973-1978 (Box 20, Folder 05-09)
  - Job Classifications, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - J, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 11-12)
  - L, 1973-1981 (Box 20, Folder 13-15)
  - M, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955-1985 (Box 20, Folder 17-18)
  - P, 1964-1983 (Box 20, Folder 19-21)
  - Reilly, James, 1981-83 (Box 20, Folder 22-25)
  - Salaried Workers, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - S, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Sections 34 and 38, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Section 36 Attendants, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Seniority Rights, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - S, 1974-1985 (Box 20, Folder 31-33)
  - Suspensions: Marijuana, [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Suspensions and Vacation Applications, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - T, 1968-1973 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Vacation Pay, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - W, 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 38-39)
  - Unemployment compensation, 1962-1965 (Box 20, Folder 40-43)
- Publications, 1955-1987; 16.610.8.
  The bulk of these files are derived from Local 610 and include general leaflets on organizing, meetings, and elections from 1955 to 1987. Additional leaflet files exist for specific topics such as Batesburg, salaried workers, and the Union Bulletin. In addition to Local 610 publications, this box also contains company publications such as the Airbrake News and Bulletin from 1967 to 1984.
  - Local 610 Leaflets: General, 1955-1987 (Box 21, Folder 01-18)
  - Local 610 Leaflets: Batesburg, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Local 610 Leaflets: Salaried Workers, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Local 610 Leaflets: Union Bulletin, 1981-1985 (Box 21, Folder 21-22)
  - Canadian Local: Strike Bulletin, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Westinghouse Airbrake Office and Technical Union, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - American Standard: Airbrake News, 1967-1984 (Box 21, Folder 25-26)
  - American Standard: Bulletins, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - American Standard: Miscellaneous, 1964-1985 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Subject Files, 1943-1987; 16.610.9.
  These files date from 1943 to 1987. The bulk of the files contain information on general topics such as the policies of American Standard, equal employment, exportation of Switch products, patents, and political action. Additional files contain correspondence with Westinghouse Airbrake Company (WABCO) managers and representatives of labor and employee relations. Occupational safety files address issues such as asbestos, general worker health and safety, and filing hazard evaluations. Additional files document the activities of the salary division of the Swissvale plant during the 1960 and 1970s.
  Extensive files exist for the transfer of work from the Wilmerding and Swissvale plants to areas in the Southern United States and Canada, such as Batesburg, South Carolina; Lexington, Kentucky; and Macon, Georgia. Several files exist for a steering committee focused on improving productivity rather than relocating jobs. This series also contains files on the "Save Our Switch" organization that developed in 1982 in response to work transfers and document the use of the National Labor Relations Board, writing to politicians, and union organizing. Files for the unemployed committee contain financial and general information on the group as well as the addresses of members. A few additional files provide information on the likelihood of future investments into the Airbrake division.
  - Absentee Control Program, 1980-1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action Program, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Airbrake Division Injunction Case: Ruling and Defendants' Memo, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Airbrake Division Injunction Case: Transcript, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Airbrake Division: Suit Against UE for Sympathy Strike, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1946-1961 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - American Standard: Articles, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - American Standard: Employee Packet, undated. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - American Standard: General, 1967-1987 (Box 22, Folder 09-10)
  - American Standard: Programs and Policies, 1982-1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Articles on Wilmerding, PA, 1963-1985 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Batesburg, South Carolina: Campaigning, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Batesburg, South Carolina: Correspondence with Company, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Batesburg, South Carolina: General, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Batesburg, South Carolina: Movement of Work, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Batesburg, South Carolina: National Labor Relations Board Charges, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Batesburg, South Carolina: Press Releases, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Blood Program, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Bureau of Employment Security, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Business Agent: Stewards Letters, 1965-1970 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Canadian Contract, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Changes in Salary and Classification, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Civil Rights Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Company Rules, 1965-1975 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Conference on Automation, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Constitution: Amendments, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Control Department Shutdown - Switch, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Conveyor Feasibility Analysis with Exhibits, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 29-30)
  - Correspondence: Airbrake Division, Employee Relations Representative, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 31-32)
  - Correspondence: Airbrake Division, General Manager, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence: Airbrake Division, Manager - Employee and Labor Relations, 1984-1986 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence: Airbrake Division, Manager - Employee Benefits and Salary, 1983-1986 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence: Airbrake Division, Manager - Union Relations, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence: Airbrake Division, Personnel Assistant, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: American Standard-Vice President-Railway Div., 1983-1986 (Box 22, Folder 38-39)
  - Correspondence: Canadian Local, 1982-1986 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence: Jobs Committee, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence: Local 610 Business Agent, 1964-1978 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence: Local 610 Members, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence: Miscellaneous, 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence: Not Sent Out, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: Public, 1983-1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Union Switch and Signal Division General, 1962-1981 (Box 23, Folder 08-09)
  - Correspondence: Union Switch and Signal Division Manager - Labor Relations, 1982-1986 (Box 23, Folder 10-12)
  - Correspondence: Union Switch and Signal Division Vice President - Employee Relations, 1982-1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Union Switch and Signal Division UE District and National Offices, 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Cost Accounting System: Switch, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Cost of Living Adjustment, 1978-1981 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Cost of Living: Inflation, 1964-1969 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Data Center, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Data Reporting: EPS/WPS, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Data Reporting: Switch, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Department Heads: Airbrake, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Disability Benefits Association Committee, 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Divisions: Switch, 1946-1968 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - East Pittsburgh, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Elections: Campaigning, 1982-1986 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Elections: Results - Local 610 Officers, 1943-1976 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Elections: Tallies, 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Electronic Test Section: Switch, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Eminent Domain: New Bedford, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Equal Employment Act, 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Equal Employment Returns, 1967-1981 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - ER Rates: Airbrake, N.D. (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Exports: Switch, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 33-40)
  - Exports: Switch, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 01-09)
  - Expulsion of Union Members, 1949-1954 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Finalists: Presidential Search, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Financial Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Flower Fund, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Garnishment Law, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Gateway Rehabilitation Center, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Group Auto Insurance, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Group Technology, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Health: Heart Disease Program, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - High Speed Transit Information, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Hours Spent on Union business - Airbrake, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Housekeeping: Switch, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Huot, Ed: Personal Notes, 1982-1986 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Industrial Products Division, Lexington, Kentucky: General, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Industrial Products Division, Lexington, Kentucky: National Labor Relations Board - General, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Industrial Products Division, Lexington, Kentucky: National Labor Relations Board - Leaflets, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Industrial Products Division, Lexington, Kentucky: Newspaper Articles, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - International Association of Machinists, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Information on Future Investments in Airbrake Division, 1983-1986 (Box 24, Folder 28-29)
  - Information on Future Investments in Switch Division, 1982-1985 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Larouche Articles, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Lease: Swissvale, 1984-1986 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Letters of Discharge, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Librarian Case: Switch, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Lost Time, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Machine Tool Auction, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Macon, Georgia: General, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Macon, Georgia: Letters From State Legislatures, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Macon, Georgia: National Labor Relations Board Cases, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Macon, Georgia: National Labor Relations Board Charges, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Macon, Georgia: National Labor Relations Board Company Response, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Macon, Georgia: National Labor Relations Board Complaint Against Switch Division, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Macon, Georgia: National Labor Relations Board Settlement, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Macon, Georgia: National Labor Relations Board Transcript, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Macon, Georgia: National Labor Relations Board UE Organizing, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Memos and Internal Correspondence: Switch, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Minimum Wage Information, 1958-1960 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-1986 (Box 25, Folder 12-13)
  - Movement of Work: Airbrake, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - National United Workers Organization, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Negotiations: Trade and Craft, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Newspaper Articles: Company, 1983-1988 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - National Labor Relation Board- Miscellaneous Charges, 1982-1985 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Occupational Safety: Asbestos, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Occupational Safety: General, 1965-1979 (Box 25, Folder 21-22)
  - Occupational Safety: Health Hazard Evaluation Determination, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - OSHA and the National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health: General, 1972-1982 (Box 25, Folder 24-26)
  - OSHA and the National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health: Link Shop Skin Cases, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - OSHA and the National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health: Tourdot Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - OSHA and the National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health: Occupational Safety and Health Committee Meetings, 1969-79 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Organizing Drives Information, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Outsourcing of Work: Letter and Related Material, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - PA Transit: Contract Forms, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - PA Transit: Contract with Union Switch and Signal Division, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Patents, 1986 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Patents, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 01-03)
  - Paternity and Maternity Leaves, 1972-1981 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Plant Closings: Legislation, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Plant Closings: Public Interest, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Petitions: Union Members, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Political Action, 1971-1979 (Box 26, Folder 08-09)
  - Political Cartoons, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Q A Relay Inspection Guide, 1977-1982 (Box 26, Folder 11-12)
  - Quality Reorganization, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Resignations from Union for Management Positions, 1980-1985 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Retirement Plan, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Salary: Additions, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Salary: Agreements, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Salary: Contract, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Salary: General, 1965-1968 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Salary: Grievances, 1965-1968 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Salary: Leaflets, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Salary: Miscellaneous, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Salary: National Labor Relations Board, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Salary: Negotiations, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Salary: Resignations, 1965-1977 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Save Our Switch: Activities, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Save Our Switch: Letters to Politicians, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Save Our Switch: Local Support, 1983-1985 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Save Our Switch: Press Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Save Our Switch: Wiring Section, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Scrap Reduction Project, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Severance Arbitration, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Severance Pay, 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Shipping Department, 1967-1977 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Short Order Rate Proposal, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Shorter Work Hours, 1959-1964 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Shutdowns, 1978-1979 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Standard Data, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Standard Hours Data, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Steering Committee: Minutes, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committee: Projects, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Steward Lists, 1974-1987 (Box 27, Folder 05-07)
  - Strike, 1969, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 08-09)
  - Subplan: Westinghouse Airbrake Company, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Tape Machines, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Time Clocks and Gates, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Trainee Program, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Transit Market Prospects, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - UE Canadian Local at Westinghouse Airbrake Company, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Unemployed Committee: Addresses, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Unemployed Committee: Financial, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Unemployed Committee: Food, 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Unemployed Committee: General, 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Unemployed Committee: TRA Related, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Unemployment Compensation Appeal, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Union Dues: Check Off Lists, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - United Auto Workers: Alliance, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Veterans: On the Job Training, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Wage Adjustments: Switch, 1967-1972 (Box 27, Folder 25-26)
  - Wage Payment Plan: Assembler - Airbrake, 1965-1966 (Box 27, Folder 27)